# HAEUN SONG

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a front-end software developer who creates functional and responsive digital products using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React and API integrations. I have a background in healthcare and health education, where I have worked as a nurse and professional program anatomy education for numerous years. With strong communication, collaboration, problem-solving and prioritization skills, I am ready to explore and find new solutions and learn new ways to code. Outside of professional work, I enjoy spending time outdoor hiking, playing soccer or snowboarding, or playing violin during orchestra rehearsals and concerts.

### **SKILLS**

HTML5 | CSS3 | SASS | JavaScript (ES6, ES5) | Version Control (Git) | Responsive Designs | Performance Testing | Communication | Prioritization | Multitasking | Leadership | Interpersonal skills | Adaptability | Teamwork & Collaboration | Critical Thinking | Continuous Learner | Teaching | Time Management | Decision Making

## **EDUCATION**

## Juno College of Technology

Web Development Bootcamp

July 2022 - Present

## University of Toronto

Honours Bachelor of Science, Nursing (BScN) Honours Bachelor of Science (BSc); Major Human Biology and Physiology Sep 2018 – Jun 2020 Sep 2014 – Apr 2018

# RECENT PROJECTS

#### Random Dice Roller

This project incorporates JavaScript to build a simple yet useful app where user can click on a play button and the number on two dices will randomly be generated. Going forward, I would like to add more features such as giving the choice to have multiple players (2+) and allowing the use to choose the number of sides on the dice.

# To-do App

This project uses JavaScript and CSS to create a simple to-do list, that allow users to input their tasks, check & uncheck the list when they complete each task. Going forward, I would like to add additional functions such as the ability to create more than one list, adding due date, reminder, notes, and other attributes to build a more interactive app.

## Bar One

This multipage-responsive website utilizes JavaScript, SASS and was built for promotion and/or advertisement of potential bar/restaurant. Bar-One has the main page where it outlines the general information about the bar and the blog page which goes into details about their new menu and displays reviews and comments written by customers. Lastly, the contact page allows for users to input messages for questions or comments which will be sent to the owners.

# PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

# University of Toronto | Gross Anatomy Lab Demonstrator and Prosector

May 2018 - Current

Division of Anatomy, Department of Surgery, Faculty of Medicine | Faculty of Dentistry

- Leading and supervising full-body cadaveric dissection to professional students with no previous dissection experiences and instructing comprehensive anatomy lab sessions for medical, dental and physiotherapy students
- Responsible for 500+ dissection and plastination of cadavers for use with various anatomy courses at the university

## The Hospital for Sick Children (SickKids)

Aug 2020 – Aug 2021

Registered Nurse | 8C: Burns, Plastic Surgery, Urology and Ophthalmology Unit

- Performed professional communication and collaboration with nurses, doctors, pharmacists, social workers, and other healthcare professionals to improve patient experience and provide care plan tailored for individual patients
- Supported patients' hospitalization journey from pre-admission to discharge by providing compassionate care for patients and families and incorporating understanding of different social determinants of health

# Sunnybrook Health Sciences Centre (Sunnybrook hospital)

June 2019 - July 2020

Clinical Extern | D3: Cardiology and Cardiovascular Surgery Unit & D7: Burns Intensive Care Unit (ICU)

- Demonstrated prioritization and time management skills whilst providing direct care to pre-operative and post-operative patients under mentorship and supervision of registered nurses.
- Provided psychosocial support for distressed patients and families and worked as a bridge between patients and the interprofessional team on unit.